Min-suk, run!
Stay away.
BEST WISHES FOR YOUR WEDDING
Wait, I…
What the…
Huh?
Oh.
Uh…
Huh.
My clothes? What the…
You're awake.
What the hell?
Who are you?
Nice to meet ya.
Byeon Ho-in, attorney at law.
BYEON HO-IN LAW OFFICE
BYEON HO-IN
You wanna win "Byeon" a reasonable doubt?
Then Ho-in is the man to call.
We have to make the most of our names
in this life, don't you think?
Just like our superpowers,
right, Sang-ung?
Hmm?
Hey, Min-suk.
Oh, Sang-ung. Tell me you're okay.
-I'm okay. What about you though?
-I'm fine, don't worry.
All right, let's get acquainted.
This girl here is Bang Eun-mi,
but she goes by Bun-mi
'cause this girl can crush a brioche.
Stop it. I hate that.
Bun-mi has the ability
to move objects with her mind
relative to the amount of calories
she's eaten.
And me, I get my powers
when I get hammered.
Min-suk can confirm that.
Okay, well, uh, what are you saying, sir?
What I'm saying is
you're not alone in the world.
We're like you.
Isn't that nice to know, that
you have companions?
Most newbies like what they hear
up till this point, so…
Well, I don't.
The water just keeps getting
deeper and deeper.
The question is, if I keep going,
can I get back to the surface?
We're the Society of Korean Superhumans.
SUPERHUMANS SOCIETY
REPRESENTATIVE, BYEON HO-IN
This is a bad idea.
-I think we should get out of here.
-Let's go.
We find superhumans
who operate in the shadows, like you,
and we take them out into the light.
That's where they belong.
Fighting for what's right.
You're doing great work,
but I like the shadows, mister,
so I'll have to pass.
-Thanks for your help. We appreciate it.
-Thanks.
And I'll be sure
to return these clothes to you
as soon as I have a minute.
Sang-ung, who do you think
burned down your home?
Oh, yeah, my apartment burned down.
-What happened?
-Min-suk, I…
-Hey, what the hell?
-There's one more thing. Won't take long.
Whoa.
Okay, follow me.
METH SMUGGLING, MASS DEATHS
HUMAN TESTING ALLEGED
BEOMHA BIO DEVELOPS VACCINE
FIRST GENE CLONING SUCCESS
BEOMHA'S FIRST GENE CLONING
The Mundane Vanguard.
"Mundane" meaning normal. No powers.
Normal everyday people
who are hunting folks like us.
Hunting, as in…
Why though?
Well, they're jealous.
We have something they never will.
And the truth is, these normies
are used to getting everything they want.
Their influence is far-reaching.
They have money, power,
access to business deals and land,
even research infrastructure.
Plenty of friends in high places too.
They have ties to the National Assembly,
government agencies,
white-shoe law firms,
corporations, the media,
and, of course,
the police and organized crime.
The entire world is on their side.
JO WON-DO
BEOMHA, MUNDANE VANGUARD HEAD
JO ANNA
BEOMHA GROUP'S HEIR
So what?
Their next target.
I have reason to believe they're
planning to bring you down.
Hello, Father.
I found the bastard who did this to you.
And now,
I can take away his extraordinary gifts.
VIP WARD
You said so yourself, didn't you?
"Hold on tight to good things, Won-do."
"Don't be a charitable fool."
What is it?
Everyone's coming out to play,
even the ones that were hiding.
Hurry things along.
Our plans will get complicated
if the lawyer gets involved.
The thing is…
…it seems Byeong has
already got to Sang-ung.
My God, you're useless.
Take care of it, or I will.
Shit.
So these people know who I am,
and they're going on the attack now?
Of course they know.
How do you think
they broke into your apartment?
How about I disappear, then?
You'd be playing right into their hands
if you tried to hide.
They made a brazen attack
in broad daylight.
Now they want you in a remote location,
so they can move on you
without drawing attention.
What am I supposed to do?
Just… pretend like it's any other day.
Huh?
Their MO with a new target is
to start by sabotaging their daily life.
You can save people,
but routine is just as important.
And in the meantime, we'll find proof
of the Vanguard's activities
and make sure
they'll be punished for it in court.
Don't worry.
With our help, you'll get your life back.
Trust me, I know it's tough, but
only you can take them on.
Our lives are in your hands.
I gotta go.
Come on.
So what made you wanna help
when you saw that bus accident
and the hotel fire?
If you had to relive those moments,
you think you could choose differently?
What kind of life do you dream of?
Think about it.
Who do you wanna be?
We're good with photos on this side.
Check for any remaining traces.
But the cable runs this way,
so I don't think it'll be affected.
-No other damage…
-Sir, over here.
Great work, everyone.
Ah.
Make sure you send this one
to the lab, okay?
-Gas explosion?
-Yeah.
Looks like it started in the bridal room,
eastern corner.
Then engulfed the whole floor.
The gas company got hit with a few fines
not too long ago
for being lazy about maintenance.
We also have statements
from some wedding guests,
saying they could smell gas
before the explosion.
CCTV footage?
It's all burnt to a crisp, sir.
We do have one video
from the scene, actually.
This clip is going viral right now.
They call him "Cashero."
-He rescued everyone during that crash.
-Is that even real?
Hey. The flames are huge. Look.
You think they can fake that?
Look at that. See that woman?
She isn't running away.
You're right.
Crazy.
Let's get a statement from her.
Uh, are you kidding? How is this training?
I need to get to work soon. Seriously?
It's a great workout.
Stop your complaining.
All right, look.
I have a feeling
that I'm a lot older than you,
so please show me some respect, all right?
Sorry, Grandpa.
-Seriously?
-Respect my elders, right?
Hurry. Put that on.
Water's heavy, bro.
-Uh-huh.
-So, Gramps, you rolling in money?
You just gonna blow through millions
whenever you wanna save a life
and end up broke?
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
-Oh wow!
Come on, you old fart. You got this!
Move it, dinosaur.
Right, since it's our first day,
just try landing one punch.
That's all?
How about if I land a punch,
I can go right home?
Good try.
Ooh!
Can I use a few won?
Sure, it's your money, right?
Really?
Still haven't hit me yet, Sang-ung.
I can't believe all that cash is gone.
Oh my God. That was 40,000 already.
Clearly, you're relying too much
on your superpowers.
For day-to-day fights,
use your own strength.
You should only use your powers
when you're in trouble. Know why?
You're broke now, you idiot.
Hurry!
It's not like I'm Usain Bolt.
You got this.
I'm ready for whatever
I am ready to roll
Every move I make, I'm breaking free
To live this moment
Not fast enough.
No worries, no more fears
Moving on here and now
Every time, every breath
Taking chances to the fullest
Never looking back
Forget about me, my yesterday
We're turning the page
Taking on the world…
Good! Right here. Here! Right here!
Forget it
Forget about yesterday
Whoo!
BEOMHA RANCH
NEEDS FURTHER INVESTIGATION
This building belongs to
the Mundane Vanguard.
The base looks like
a normal cattle company, right?
However, it's where
they run experiments on superhumans.
Our goal is to sabotage their operations
and collect information.
Did you say "our"?
-So you want me to go?
-Yeah, obviously.
It's restricted
and crawling with security.
Checkpoints will be monitored by guards.
You need to get us through.
I need to?
I'd be happy to switch with you.
You can be the one
to bust open the meter-thick steel door.
No, I'll get us through.
We're in business, then.
I need to figure out
an airtight strategy for the raid.
So why don't you keep up your training
till we're ready?
It's a present.
-Hmm.
-Oh boy.
You got me a…
You shouldn't carry money in your pockets.
These will help.
They'll keep all the change from spilling.
Even my girlfriend
of nine years has never dared
to give me tighty-whities as a gift.
It'll complicate things for us
if your identity ever gets revealed,
so cover your face.
This feels like something
a criminal would wear.
The minute I saw that mask,
it reminded me of someone.
Hey.
-You got cash?
-What are you doing?
Who the fuck carries around
a bag with no cash?
Wait, please, just wait.
Hey!
-Shit, you snuck up on me.
-What the hell?
Who are you?
Me?
I'm just passing through.
Looking back, I've always been the person
who'd walk by and say nothing.
If there was a little girl
taking donations for the Salvation Army,
I would pass right by.
Once, I even saw an old man
getting roughed up by some thugs,
and I just kept walking.
-I think you ought to move on, cowboy.
-Not gonna happen.
I'm sick of guys like you
preying on innocent people.
You're parasites,
and I won't put up with it anymore.
What's he doing?
We should snatch that right now.
You got a lot of cash.
10,000 won should be plenty for you guys.
Fuck! Get her!
You piece of shit!
Don't let him get away!
Goddammit, now you're dead.
Son of a bitch! Hey, you good?
Motherfucker!
He's pretty good.
Let's get out of here.
Hey, honey?
I thought you said you sold this.
-Yeah! I did it!
-Right there. Jump now! All right!
Great job, sweetheart!
-Woo-hoo!
-Yes!
Just passing through.
Just a guy… passing through.
Hell yeah.
I was just passing through.
I can't let this slide.
Now you're gonna pay.
Don't tell me you were wearing
that around, were you?
Uh…
I have to protect my identity.
That is so embarrassing.
You can't walk around the neighborhood
dressed like a bank robber.
I think you should do your training
at least a half dozen subway stops away
from now on.
-All right?
-I can continue training?
I'll take the cash out of your allowance.
But you're just lucky
it's cheaper than my skincare.
I'll just think of it
as donating to charity or something.
But listen, in return,
I need you to cross your heart
and swear to God
you won't empty another account.
It's all right.
I don't even have the money.
-Uh-huh.
-Wait, this seems kinda sudden.
I mean, what changed?
I won the housing lottery.
HOUSING LOTTERY RESULTS
KIM MIN-SUK
Hey! Oh my God!
Holy crap! Oh my God! Min-suk!
Wow! When the heck did this happen?
The same time you were
trying to save the world, I guess.
We got the newlywed special.
-This is unreal.
-Mm-hmm.
Hang on. Did we actually tie the knot?
You signed the registration certificate.
You were busy,
so I went and filed it alone.
Oh, wow.
Osan?
Osan's actually pretty central, you know?
Mm-hmm.
-Wow.
-Sang-ung.
The next thing on the list is
to get serious about saving.
-Mm-hmm.
-Sixty million won paid up front is a lot.
Uh, I'll drain my savings accounts
plus my checking.
And if my parents both help,
the down payment should be covered.
Mm. But the second payment,
how are we gonna cover it?
There's a job opening for twice my salary,
so I interview in the morning.
Whoa. A big shot, huh?
No way!
Ah, right.
What else you got?
This month's allowance. Here ya go.
Uh, much appreciated.
Mm-hmm.
Five, ten, fifteen, twenty, twenty-five.
Yep, um…
50,000?
You put an extra 50K in here.
Yeah, uh,
so most of it's for your training.
And the other 50,000 is
so I can experiment with you.
Oh, really?
-Uh, so these powers you have.
-Mm-hmm.
You said the more money you get,
the stronger you are, right?
Mm-hmm.
Then does that affect your whole body?
Like, every part… the whole thing?
-Well, yeah, I think.
-Hmm.
So, um, with 50,000 won…
-About how long could you last?
-What?
Ah…
Hmm?
I'm not sure, but I think…
I think we should probably, um,
experiment and find out.
Oh, really?
Every heart
Every glance
Feels like a sweet, sweet dance
You turned my night to days…
Wow, your body is slammin' right now.
Must be all the water I've been loading.
It's better
I will never stray
In my life, every day felt like a maze
Without a clue, without a trace…
Hurry up.
Put your money where your mouth is.
Just you wait. I'm gonna blow your mind.
-God, Sang-ung!
-What? What is it?
-You're so strong all of a sudden.
-Told ya.
Mr. Kang is passing through, baby!
-Where is Gi?
-He's getting treatment.
Fuck. I'm surprised it's taking this long.
What the hell?
He has injuries, so his body might be
too weak to withstand it.
Nowadays, competence isn't enough
to keep someone employed.
Don't you think it's worth it to try
giving him a chance before he passes,
instead of just letting him die?
Consider it a health-enhancing dose.
Administer it.
Is that a no?
How about we make you take it?
So where are we driving?
Um, where are we going?
To bring in some bad guys.
All right. Let's get it all out of here.
You mean we're unloading those?
We need to deliver them
to every home we see.
Wait. You said
there'd be enemies to fight here?
The worst enemy
that every poor person faces
is the cold.
Ah.
-Thinking about using that strength?
-I don't… I don't have any money.
But you guys go on ahead.
Hey, old man. I'm at the back door.
Yeah, come on in.
Bread girl.
Whose house is this?
-It's Old Man Do's.
-Who is Old Man Do? What's his deal?
A fellow superhuman. He's geriatric.
His superpower is what exactly?
He has an extraordinary gift.
More valuable than any of ours.
Old Man Do sees the future.
He has the wisdom to let you know
if you're ready.
You can come in.
THE LORD IS MY SHEPHERD. I SHALL NOT WANT
PSALM 23:1
-You're Dong-gi's son, aren't you?
-That's right.
-So you're penniless then, right?
-Huh?
Yeah.
Looking at this shack,
you wouldn't know I'm rich, right?
Definitely not.
So has Samsung finally topped out
at 10,000 won?
We're onto stocks?
No, I'm pretty sure that, uh, Samsung,
uh, plateaued around 60,000. Yeah.
Goddamn it.
Maybe I should've pulled out at 80, huh?
Look, I'm here because they said
you'd know if I'm ready to actually,
ya know, join the society.
Sure. That's right.
Let me get a good look at your eyes.
Oh God. What's happening now?
Oh shit! Sorry! Excuse me.
The gold's shine
loses its gleam in the dark.
So take heed, young man.
Your power can cease to shine.
Uh, but wait. What do you mean?
Only when you put your fate at hazard,
like throwing coins into a well
as a child,
only then might… the gold
regain its brilliant sheen.
I'm not sure what you're saying.
Uh, sir?
Hey, old man Do! Oh!
You're Dong-gi's son, aren't you?
Yeah. Yes.
You're penniless, then. Right?
Yeah.
What did he tell you?
Well, I'm confused.
I think the old man's
a little crazy, actually.
He was blabbering,
his eyes were all white.
Oh, right.
I'm sure he probably said
only what he had to.
The man can't remember the past,
even though he sees the future.
We're all like that to some degree.
We lose it all.
Health, money, precious memories.
Can't do anything about it.
Guess not.
Bun-mi.
Get over here.
What for?
I owe you one.
Was that respect?
Oh God, stop it.
Our enemy is here.
Okay, out, out. Hurry up, let's move it!
All right. Everyone, up the hill!
They're over there! This way, hurry up!
Bun-mi, get the old man
to a secure location.
Sang-ung.
Yeah?
-Here.
-Thanks.
You better run.
Huh?
You get captured, we're done for.
There's a retaining wall.
-That should be enough to get over it.
-Hang on. But then you'll be alone, right?
Well, it's an alley.
I'll block it up, okay?
-Hang on a sec.
-Go already!
Oh!
Go, go, go!
You're all going down!
Push through!
God, seriously.
CHAIRWOMAN PARK JEONG-JA
What?
What do you want me to do for you?
What the hell are you talking about?
You sound like a lunatic.
Look, you've been after me
'cause of my dad.
You said you wanted me
to marry your daughter.
It's 'cause you need me
to do something for you, right?
Come on. I know you don't really care
about his debts.
Listen, you need to stop blathering
and pay me in full.
I'll do it.
Whatever it is, I'll do it.
Whatever it is, you'll do it?
In return…
I need you to give me a loan.
People only call when they get desperate.
It's so strange.
Sorry about the call.
That was actually
my future son-in-law on the phone.
Ah. I see. That's fine.
So your name is Kim Min-suk.
Yes.
I'm excited to get to know you.
Okay, let's stop.
-Hey, old man, you okay?
-I'm okay.
-Bun-mi, you all right? You sure?
-Yeah, I'm fine. All good.
-Stop!
-Hey, hey, hey!
Did you really think you'd be safer,
causing all this commotion
in broad daylight?
So everybody's here, huh?
You having a team-building dinner?
You know,
we really should've met like this sooner.
All right.
Kang Sang-ung. Where is he now?
I've waited such a long time
to see you like this, in the flesh.
I have to get a good look
at a person's eyes
to get a proper glimpse into their future.
I'm sorry?
Soon, that cruel bastard will return.
Your home will be yours no longer.
Death will come for you
sooner than you think.
The gun you're going to fire
will one day aim at you.
You know, I think I need
to go up a size in underwear.
Look at this mess. I can't fit it all in.
Sang-ung, good to see ya!
-Hey, old geezer.
-I thought we talked about that.
Old Man Do.
Kang Sang-ung.
The one and only.
This isn't just any cash.
It's a predatory loan
from a seedy organization.
The interest rate is sky-high.
If I default on even one payment,
my whole future goes up in flames.
Hey, look out!
The need for money never ends.
As soon as the paycheck hits your account,
it's drained by everything
from family obligations to utility bills.
The costs keep piling up.
Just like these bastards.
RECHARGE YOUR CALORIES!
Oh God.
Shit!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Get away from me!
Son of a bitch. Is that…
Huh?
What's wrong?
Out of money already, you little wimp?
You been getting your pump on?
Impressive physique.
Why'd he do that?
Oh!
If I come in close, I get scorched.
If I back off, I get pummeled.
What the hell do I do?
I can fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
Try to fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine
Give me all the cash
I feel the fire now
Try to punch you, smash
Devil is into your mind
I am cynical, but I feel powerful
I can crush you now
Time is done you better run
Let me whisper to your mind
You will feel the burn
Supernatural
I got the power on my mind
I can give you all the pain
Till the break of dawn
I can fly up the sky
Every day and night
Drop it on the floor
Better listen now
You got nothing
And I know that this is over now
Chasing you around
Round merry-go-round
Boo, I got you
You will never see the light
Let me whisper to your mind
You will feel the burn
Supernatural
I got the power on my mind
I can give you all the pain
Till the break of dawn
I can fly up the sky
Every day and night
Burn the lonely eyes
Crucify your lies
Now you cry
You better run
Run it speed of light
You better run, run it till you fight
Pain through your heart
Pain through your soul
It's time
I can fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
Try to fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine
No one else can find you now
Only devils on your side
You will see the darkest night
I can fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
Try to fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine